[Waco] Branch Davidians: Mark Swett collection, Inclusive: 1921-2001, undated, Bulk: 1978-1993
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Audio Recordings, 1976-1995, undated; 4
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 244, April 18, 1993 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape 50, undated (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - Cassette Tape: SW3, undated (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - Cassette Tape: “Mad Man in Waco”, undated (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 13)
  - Cassette Tape: “Seventh Angel”, undated (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 14)
  - Cassette Tape: NPR Radio: Davidian Women, undated (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 15)
  - Cassette Tape: General, undated (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 16)
  - Cassette Tape: David Koresh and David Bunds, February 21, 1991 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 17)
  - Cassette Tape: “Clips” (1 of 3), undated (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 18)
  - Cassette Tape: “Clips” (2 of 3), undated (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 19)
  - Cassette Tape: “Clips” (3 of 3), undated (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 20)
  - Cassette Tape: Dr. Arnold and Dr. Tabor, undated (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 21)
  - Compact Disk: Benjamin Roden, 1977-1978 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 22)
  - Compact Disk: David Koresh Music, undated (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 23)
  - Compact Disk: Koresh Secret Recordings, undated (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 24)
  - Compact Disk: SDA Church: Hawaii, undated (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 25)
  - Compact Disk: David Koresh: Voice of Fire, 1993 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 26)
  - Compact Disk: Koresh/Bunds, 1984-1990 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 27)
  - Cassette Tape: David Koresh #1, 1993 February 28 (Box 19 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape #6, 1993 February 28 (Box 19 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape #217, 1993 February 28 (Box 19 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Cassette Tape: David Koresh, 1993 March 2 (Box 19 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape #31, 1993 March 3 (Box 19 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape #31A, 1993 March 3 (Box 19 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape #76, 1993 March 7 (Box 19 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape #80, 1993 March 7 (Box 19 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape #42, 1993 March 9 (Box 19 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape #140, 1993 March 19 (Box 19 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape #217, 1993 April 13 (Box 19 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape #219, 1993 April 13 (Box 19 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape #221, 1993 April 13 (Box 19 OVZ, Folder 13)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape #235, 1993 April 16 (Box 19 OVZ, Folder 14)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape #24, 1993 April 17 (Box 19 OVZ, Folder 15)
  - Cassette Tape: Surveillance, 1993 April 18 (Box 19 OVZ, Folder 16)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape #240, 1993 April 18 (Box 19 OVZ, Folder 17)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape #245, 1993 April 19 (Box 19 OVZ, Folder 18)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape #247, 1993 April 19 (Box 19 OVZ, Folder 19)
  - Cassette Tape: “Songs to Grandpa”: David Koresh, 1996 (Box 19 OVZ, Folder 20)
  - Cassette Tape: Clips #2, undated (Box 19 OVZ, Folder 21)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape #41, undated (Box 19 OVZ, Folder 22)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape #58, undated (Box 19 OVZ, Folder 23)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape #67: Day 1 Negotiations, undated (Box 19 OVZ, Folder 24)
  - Cassette Tape: Tape #99, undated (Box 19 OVZ, Folder 25)
  - Cassette Tape: W. Martin and Agent, undated (Box 19 OVZ, Folder 26)
  - Cassette Tape: Steve Schneider (1 of 3), 1990 January 15 (Box 20 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Cassette Tape: Steve Schneider (2 of3), 1990 January 15 (Box 20 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Cassette Tape: Steve Schneider (3 of 3), 1990 January 15 (Box 20 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Cassette Tape: Steve Schneider (1 of 3), 1990 January 16 (Box 20 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Cassette Tape: Steve Schneider (2 of3), 1990 January 16 (Box 20 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Cassette Tape: Steve Schneider (3 of 3), 1990 January 16 (Box 20 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Cassette Tape: Steve Schneider (1 of 3), 1990 January 19 (Box 20 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - Cassette Tape: Steve Schneider (2 of3), 1990 January 19 (Box 20 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - Cassette Tape: Steve Schneider (3 of 3), 1990 January 19 (Box 20 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - Cassette Tape: David Koresh Letter to Steve Schneider and Wisconsin Brethren, 1987 (Box 20 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - Cassette Tape: David Koresh: “Sabbath” (1 of 2), undated (Box 20 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - Cassette Tape: David Koresh: “Sabbath” (2 of 2), undated (Box 20 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - Cassette Tape: David Koresh: “Loud Cry”, 1985 (Box 20 OVZ, Folder 13)
  - Cassette Tape: David Koresh: “The Bird”, 1987 August 24 (Box 20 OVZ, Folder 14)
  - Cassette Tape: David Koresh: “Foundation”, 1989 October (Box 20 OVZ, Folder 15)
  - Cassette Tape: David Koresh: “Seven Angels”, undated (Box 20 OVZ, Folder 16)